<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Emily DEVELOPMENT Journey</title>
    <link href="https://emilyc206.fyi/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://emilyc206.fyi" />
    <updated>2025-08-26T18:59:22-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>EmilyC206</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://emilyc206.fyi</id>

    <entry>
        <title>DEFCON 33</title>
        <author>
            <name>EmilyC206</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://emilyc206.fyi/defcon-33.html"/>
        <id>https://emilyc206.fyi/defcon-33.html</id>

        <updated>2025-08-18T05:02:40-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    DEFCON 33 represents the influential information security conferences in America.Tracing back to 1993, the convention was hosted by Jeff Moss, AKA Dark Tangent, as a farewell party for a fellow hacker moving abroad. Today, it is amassive annual convention with thousands of attendees, including nerds&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>DEFCON 33 represents the influential information security conferences in America.Tracing back to 1993, the convention was hosted by Jeff Moss, AKA <em>Dark Tangent</em>, as a farewell party for a fellow hacker moving abroad. Today, it is  amassive annual convention with thousands of attendees, including nerds like myself. I would describe the core of DEFCON to be a community space; a space for people curious about technology to come together. <br><br>Everybody there was keen to share knowledge, demonstrate vulnerabilities, and push the boundaries of computing and security. For myself, I volunteered in the embedded systems villages dedicated to hardware hacking, pcb design, wireless security, and even social engineering as a whole.</p>
<p>I had a great time taking part in this tradition. That I had a chance to blends serious security research with CTFs and "Cultural exchange". So remember, our goal is to celebrate openness, curiosity, and self improvments. I'm very glad to be a part of hacker history.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>IT 125 Database Moment</title>
        <author>
            <name>EmilyC206</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://emilyc206.fyi/it-125-database-moment.html"/>
        <id>https://emilyc206.fyi/it-125-database-moment.html</id>

        <updated>2025-07-16T18:44:52-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Let me introduce to you IT125.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Let me introduce to you IT125.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hello World / IT 125</title>
        <author>
            <name>EmilyC206</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://emilyc206.fyi/hello-world-it-125.html"/>
        <id>https://emilyc206.fyi/hello-world-it-125.html</id>

        <updated>2025-07-11T16:00:45-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    &nbsp;Be it industry trends, consumer management, or automating data-collection, I craft tech-stack features into the sales tool of tommorow. Self-taught and Google-certified for AGILE project management, I focus on continuous deployment and iterative team development. Here's a picture of me practicing photography!
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    &nbsp;Be it industry trends, consumer management, or automating data-collection, I craft tech-stack features into the sales tool of tommorow. Self-taught and Google-certified for AGILE project management, I focus on continuous deployment and iterative team development.
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/000048300012.jpg" height="2075" width="3130" alt=""  sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" srcset="https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/responsive/000048300012-xs.jpg 640w ,https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/responsive/000048300012-sm.jpg 768w ,https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/responsive/000048300012-md.jpg 1024w ,https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/responsive/000048300012-lg.jpg 1366w ,https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/responsive/000048300012-xl.jpg 1600w ,https://emilyc206.fyi/media/posts/1/responsive/000048300012-2xl.jpg 1920w">
      <figcaption>Here's a picture of me practicing photography!</figcaption>
    </figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
